I'm going to ask you about Mike.
When you were the OC,
what was it like working with him as the
OC and
what what is it that you like and
admire? What did you learn from him?
Yeah, Mike is a great coach. I had a
great experience with Mike in Dallas for
a few years and
learned a ton of football. He's got a
great operation system.
I think it it was one of those things
that helped prepare me for when I had
the opportunity to come in these shoes
and be a head football coach and he's
done it for a really long time.
So being the OC, I mean he's calling the
plays, but what did what was your
responsibility? How did that evolve?
Yeah, obviously
as we went through our process there,
you know, I was an offensive coordinator
the previous year and I was fortunate
enough to stay on when when Mike became
the head coach. Still calling plays and
but we were we were having a lot of
conversations through the entire week
and so I helped prepare me. Is he a very
detailed oriented guy? Yeah, no doubt.
Yep.
Intense?
Yeah, I think I think Mike has a focus
to him and in a good way that
again I think he's just got a really
good system and operation allows teams
to be very successful. Thanks, man. Yep.
Yeah, no I I think we're really excited
to have an opportunity to sign Zach. Um
Okay, we had two quarterbacks. We're
going we're going to need to sign some
more and our job is always to
make those environments as competitive
as possible.
You know, we feel good about watching
Zach over the time of his journey.
Um
have followed him, evaluated him a
number of times now and so I felt like
the opportunity is right. We we feel
really good about, you know, obviously
Tyler and Spencer and we feel feel like
those both those guys progressed really
well last year and so you know, there's
always competition every NFL
environment, but I think it'll be a
really good spot for us.
Yeah, I mean Zach's 26 years old. It's
really the same age as the rest of our
quarterback room and so his journey's
taken him some different spots.
Um
You know, again you do some homework on
it. You evaluate everything.
Yeah, I think this will be a great
opportunity for him that being a I think
hopefully a healthy environment from the
quarterback perspective and
you know, just continue to grow and
develop cuz he's still got plenty of
that available to us.
I certainly think he's got some
experience that he can lean on.
Both probably experiences he feels
really good about and some experiences
that he got to learn from and every
quarterback has that and so You know,
Zach went through a lot early early in
New York.
Wasn't without some success and some
some good moments. You know, I think you
know, you certainly recognize those and
then his experience going to Denver. I
think that was a really healthy
situation for him. Thought he that
preseason film at Denver was really
really good. I think
now since we have ties and you know,
kind of know what that operation looked
like for him and so we feel like we can
provide provide an opportunity for him
just to get better as a quarterback.
Yep, absolutely love Foster.
A+ person.
Just an awesome awesome leader for our
team. He was coming off an injury for
us. He didn't play right away and so the
leadership that he showed our team
through a little bit of a challenging
early part of the season was really
special and so
you know, I'm excited for his future. He
can still play. He still plays at a
really high level and so
he'll be a excellent contribution you
know, to that tight end room.
Yeah, I think I think he's just got he's
he's persevered through a lot,
but also
his smile and his excitement each and
every day in the building is very
contagious and I think it helps
everyone.
Yep.
Yeah, there's conversations and that's
what this time of year is all about and
so um
you know, that's that's obviously the
business side of this thing that
inevitably comes up. Um
Everyone's a part of that. Everyone
knows those things come up and so it's
just about you know, a working
relationship for everyone just to find
what works best for everyone and to find
a good situation. So obviously we we
know we love Chris and
we're excited about his future.
Yeah, I think anytime
you know, obviously you just it becomes
a a situation where you understand where
it's going to be. But but again, these
timelines are all different. I think
it's hard to you know, try and say
everyone has to follow the same
timelines. There's a lot of
conversations, a lot of variables that
go into those things.
We love Chris. It's been a really good
conversation. I know from a business
side and we'll just continue to keep
working through that.
Yeah,
really excited about the signing Travis.
You know, obviously Alvin you know, we
love Alvin. He means the world to all of
us.
You know, again this is a full off
season process. Certainly we feel like
hey,
he's in that room. You know, you can you
can find roles for all those different
guys. We'll go through the whole off
season process and you know, continue to
grow and develop this team.
Well, yeah, he's certainly on on the
roster and you know, part of that
running back room and we we feel like
there's ways that you can manipulate all
those guys and put them in
playing situations. Again,
look at our season last year, look at
probably just about every NFL season.
Plenty of running backs play. You know,
obviously we feel fortunate that we were
able to acquire Travis in free agency,
but
you know, there's there's still a lot of
work to be had out there.
Yeah, I think they're they're probably
similar players.
You know, I think both of them obviously
have the explosive elusive ability, can
play in all three phases which is
beneficial and so you know, I feel
[snorts] like where our running back
room is a really healthy room right now
with just the depth and the experience
and all the all the guys that are in
there.
Yeah, I I think you know, there's a lot
of different ways you can do this.
Our running back room, you know, with
the way last season went,
a lot of those guys got experience. A
lot of those guys played football and so
it's going to be a benefit for us that
you know,
you know, we we got
a few guys, three or four guys that
played meaningful snaps last year that
are all coming back and then you throw
Travis into the mix and you know, it's a
great situation for us.
Yeah, that's a good question. I think
you know, the timing of everything. You
know, obviously you know, there's a play
clock and it happens fast. You got a few
seconds to make a decision. You got to
go.
And then I think the the challenge but
also fun element is when you got to kind
of navigate some things, some unexpected
situations during a during a game.
Whether be an adjustment from a scheme
perspective, a personnel issue, whatever
it may be and you got to just have those
conversations, you know, kind of go
through as many of them as you can
before it, but understand you know,
things are going to come up.
Yeah, I I think each and every week it's
just like a player you get more and more
comfortable with it and you go through
more and more experiences both
positively and negatively and you're
going to have calls you love, you're
going to have calls you want back.
That's going to happen every game and no
matter how long you call call games,
you're going to have the same feeling
after games.
It's about learning from those
experiences and growing and you know,
preparing yourself more.
Yeah.
Yeah, excellent player, excellent
person. Been around a bunch of
successful programs. He knows what it
needs to look like and just felt like it
was a really good fit for us and so we
feel very fortunate.
Yeah, I think credit to Audric. He came
in the middle of the season and to be,
you know, really quickly right after
that on the field playing executing at a
really high level. I think credit to his
preparation. He did an excellent job
there and
yeah, he's part of a running back room
that we have we have some depth now
because of this and so obviously really
beneficial. I was fired up for him.
Obviously
performed really well late in the
season.
Yeah, anytime you have continuity, you
get to kind of build off of the previous
year and add a little layer to it and so
you know, similar to just what we're
doing as a coaching staff this year. We
have a lot of continuity in our staff, a
lot of continuity from a player's
perspective and so we're able to stack
those things and so we're able to go
through an evaluation of the past year
and say all right, this is where we're
at. Now here's where we're going.
No, I think that's a real that's that's
a really good observation.
Quarterbacks when they go through the
portal or when there's just constant
staff changes which is happening very
common in college football right now.
Feels like sometimes you're relearning,
you know,
day one stuff constantly every single
year and so you're kind of going back
through level 100 instead of kind of
graduating and going to the next stage
and so that's just a balancing act
everyone's playing in college football
because you know, the staffs there's a
lot of changes always.
You know, there's a lot of movement on
the coaching side of it and then the
player side of it is equally the same
amount of movement.
>> I think he's never going to get to
300-300.
How does that make you affect the way
you feel here?
I think it's just having an
understanding where the player is at and
where he needs to go and
all these guys are going to grow. They
they got to grow. That's part of the
journey. It's part part of also of our
responsibility of kind of recognizing
where they're at. What are they most
comfortable with and can be most
successful when they come out on the
field and so uh you know, that's the
focus of ours and then continue to build
them as we go. And that having a having
a second year just this being your
second draft process like what's
different from just the familiarity and
kind of knowing everyone and knowing how
to talk
Yeah, I'd say, you know, from a staff
perspective working with coaching and
scouting and personnel and you know,
we've had a full calendar year that
we've been together and so obviously
we've had a lot more conversations.
We've had a lot more of those dialogues
of making sure we're all on the same
page. And then the second part of it the
the selfish part of it is just the
the exposure. You know, last year you
know, coming in and you're kind of in a
little bit of a speedy speedy process.
This year you know, I feel really
comfortable with you know, the stages
we've gone through the conversations
we've already had about the draft
process the prospects.
Just have a much better feel for where
everything is at. Do you watch a lot
like during the season college football
what's going on like are you doing
Saturdays like We'll catch some here and
there more from a fan perspective so not
necessarily evaluating but you know,
there's guys that catch your attention
or you catch a guy on a Saturday night
meal and you know, send send Jeff a text
about hey who's this guy who just caught
this touchdown passes so
you know, it's a fun process. And Kyler
I'm curious it seems like the 18 game
schedule is coming whether it's in a few
years or what
From a coach's perspective
how do you look at if it does become an
18 game slate
how do you change alter maybe approach
you know, what do you think are the
biggest obstacles trying to deal with an
elongated schedule?
Yeah, I think it's just scheduling.
Obviously, you know, we we play a number
of games and you know, if you do
preseason and you go all the way to
Super Bowl I mean it's it's you know,
whatever 23 24 games and so there's a
lot of games on on the calendar. I think
it's you know, more important from a
management and workload perspective
managing those those things for the
players and understand that you know,
one more week of all that it's only one
week and that's that's another big wear
and tear on these guys and so you got to
be conscious of that. Is there something
to be said too about like maybe they
scale back OTAs obviously still have
training camp 12 for a month like as a
coach do you think about like do we
maybe make it a little bit lighter just
because you know, you've got even a
longer grind ahead with an extra game?
It's a good question. That's something
we you know, if we get to that stage or
when we get to that stage however we
want to look at it
you know, just understand those numbers
and really studying it and finding
ultimately a really good acclimation
plan cuz our guys got to be ready to go.
They got to be
training camp there's no other
environment to practice the physicality
and the pads and kind of the
the physical components of the of the
game and then once you get in the season
obviously there's a limited exposure
that as you go and so you just got to
balance out both of those. How would you
pick sorry go ahead. Thank you. As
you're going through that onboarding
process with a young quarterback what
are some of the key things you're
looking at initially
what do you look at to say okay, I know
he's ready.
Yeah, I think just going through Kyler's
experience I'd say
um
every quarterback is going to come from
a different foundation recognize that
continue to grow
a lot of times early in the off season
they're just trying to understand the
system and so the results while they are
relevant they're not the most important
thing always
you know, I think Kyler's a great
example of you know, during training
camp I mean he's figuring things out
he's being exposed to something for the
first time and so that's an important
part of it to let him just go through
that process. And then once we got to
the regular season you know, we went
with Spencer. I felt like Spencer was
playing his best football during
training camp. He was ready to go
and then Kyler I think was in a great
environment just to continue to grow as
a player and and get it as much exposure
as he as he did and so
you know, you got to take advantage of
being a scout team quarterback. That's a
great opportunity. That's a great
environment. Kyler was able to you know,
deal with muddy pockets you know, where
it's not always clean and that's going
to happen in the league. Test your arm
test your test your ability to throw the
football can I make that throw can I not
make that throw. When you do it on the
in a practice environment like that you
can put yourself as much in a game
environment as you can but also test
yourself put yourself
push the boundaries and then find your
common space and your your your spot
where you feel like you're playing your
best football and so Kyler got to that
point as the season progressed and you
know, he was ready to go. And having
played the game before in that position
specifically how much does that help you
like being on the same page being able
to see
the game through the eyes of the
quarterback and calling
Yeah, I think that's that's ultimately
the the key to all this
if you're the play caller head coach
the quarterback ultimately you know,
having as many conversations as you have
you can during the week
understanding you know, kind of the the
viewpoint of everyone and then putting
yourself in the best position to be
successful.
And then just Kyler being around is that
a benefit like in the off season Kyler
is staying local being at the facility
like how how does that all work for I
think it makes I think it's great for
the city.
>> [laughter]
>> He's he's at every event. I'm trying to
see if
Yeah, no Kyler Kyler's been great.
Obviously
you know, those guys again the big thing
for all of our guys is the off season
process. You have this window from the
end of the season to OTAs you have this
little window and there's a ton of
flexibility within our within our guys
schedule and I think it's important to
have the right kind of guys
because they need to have their own
structure and their own plan and their
own vision for what this these few
months have to look like and Kyler's a
great example. I think you know, he's
just he's got a plan. He's organized.
He's ready to go. He's getting better
and so that when he shows up in April
it's not you know, loosen up the joints
and let's start throwing the football
again. He he's already had a process and
he's already been getting better. Is he
implementing some of the things like
you guys talked with him at the end of
the season like hey we want to work on
this like are you kind of seeing him
implement those things and what is he
working on?
Yeah, I mean I'll leave that up to him
as far as his conversations. I think
he's
you know, every guy's got to get better.
Every every guy gets gets to get better
as we go through this journey. I think
all these guys again just having a plan
having a purpose for what they do not
just going out there just to do it
you know, and get better and so there's
a stage of this time of year which is
really you know, it's their own
individual time they're able to focus on
the items they want. We'll get into the
OTA phase. We'll kind of reconvene for a
few months there and then we'll have a
little summer break and then training
camp and so there's there's a few stages
to this off season but again our guys
just got to keep growing. Do you think
free agency helped with the draft just
in terms of what you guys did
opening up for
how do you think that all helps? Yeah, I
I think free agency was a really good
process. I thought um
Mickey and our personnel group Mike
Randy those guys on the pro side I
thought they did an excellent job of
being having a clear objective
identifying guys that fit what we maybe
looking for really the right kind of
guys as well and so I felt like it was a
really clean operation we're able to
kind of add some really key pieces to us
that allows us to kind of you know,
everyone hopes and everyone says the
same thing. Everyone hopes that you can
go into the draft saying hey kind of
however this thing falls we have some
flexibility within this draft because
there's always unpredictability of who's
going to get drafted above you and so I
feel like we're in a healthy spot in
that in that case. How does that process
work with you know, you guys like what
does it look like?
The uh Just like the player acquisition
process free agency like are you guys
putting it all together like how just
kind of kind of how does it get
together? I think yeah, there's pro side
and there's college side and you know,
there's plenty of overlapping within
that and so you know, our pro side I
think does an excellent job of really
there's a lot of pro players that are
potential targets. It's narrowing our
focus into exactly what we want from
whether it be a scheme perspective a
roster fit you know, kind of putting the
pieces together.
They do an excellent job Mike and Randy
and those guys do an excellent job of
kind of narrowing our focus and then it
allows us to kind of have those
conversations on the handful of guys
that would probably fit our criteria.
We're able to acquire some of those guys
which is awesome and now we shift to the
college process and and the pro side is
a year round process. I think that's one
of the big things that goes goes on is
you know, everyone sees this week of all
these big contracts that come out free
agency and it's this big you know, it's
an exciting time for certainly for a lot
of organizations.
But that's going to happen before the
draft that's going to certainly happen
right after the draft. June there's you
know, moves that are made right before
training camp there's moves that that
are made. You can look at our you know,
last year the guys we acquired at the
end of August. Um
it's a year round process. Are you are
you like these are the guys I have to
have or is it more to collaborate like
what what's the uh Yeah, no I think I
think it's a really collaborative
process. I think it's coaches
identifying from a scheme and a roster
standpoint hey here's kind of what we're
looking for. Pro guys kind of being able
to look at it from a league wide
perspective what maybe fits those
umbrellas and then us having those
conversations to kind of tie it all
together.
Jets signed Demario Davis in free
agency. Yep. Can you talk about the
value he can provide
on the field for your young team also
inside the locker room? Yeah, I think
Demario is an excellent leader. He's
going to be great for the Jets. His
leadership in the locker room on the
field the way he the example that he
sets you know, every day in practice in
games.
Obviously performed at a really high
level last year and so
you know, I think it's going to be great
for great for all those guys up there to
have him in that locker room. I think
he's going to raise the level for all
those guys. Since he's helping guys on
the team like Ty and Sauce and Alontae
Taylor. I know it was just one year but
what were some of the things that you
really liked about his skill set what
stood out to you? Yeah, Alontae's
versatility was obviously beneficial his
ability to play inside and outside his
play making ability. He's a really
talented corner his best football is
probably ahead of him. You know, I think
he's going to play some really good
football for him and have a huge impact.
Yeah, he seemed to play I think it was
like
600 snaps or so in the slot. Yeah.
What about his skill set do you think
fits that role that
fits you know, personal wise?
I think when you go inside at that
nickel slash star position it's
important that obviously there's a
coverage component. There's a lot of
variables so you have to be able to
process a lot of football rather quickly
cuz you're seeing you know, you're just
in the action. And then his ability to
play in the run game and his ability to
blitz I think would beneficial is his
ability to blitz you know, he's he's had
some sacks in his career as been very
big time moments and so he'll play
really well for him. How do you guys go
about trying to replace
someone you kind of want to keep in the
room?
Alante?
Yeah, yeah. It's obviously going to be a
challenge. I think we got some guys in
our building. Obviously, we feel like
can make that transition
both from the corner and the safety
buckets so to speak. Sometimes that
position has some
variables that tie both those positions
together.
Again, we'll go through the draft
process. We'll see what comes out of
that that experience and then you know,
we'll continue to evaluate it.
I think it's an important position in
our defense just you know, because
you're so interconnected with all
aspects of the the scheme. You know,
you're you're part of the run fits.
You're involved in the run game. You're
part of the pressure plan. You have to
be tied in with the coverage. You know,
there's going to be some hard downs
where you have to play you know, some
man-to-man
in those positions and so
you know, it's going to take some
versatility. We feel like we do have
some guys in our building that
can play that position. You know,
obviously there's a training component
that has to go with that and then we'll
just let this whole off-season process
take its course.
No, no, no, we we haven't.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, we love Cam. Obviously, we
think the world of Cam and so again,
it's it's an off-season process. It's a
free agency process that every team and
player get to have and so you know, we
obviously will let that process take its
course. Obviously, we love Cam and so
we'll see where it takes us you know,
for him for him as as his situation you
know, goes through.
Yeah, I think those are all just the the
fun healthy conversations that we all
get to have and so obviously, we love
Cam and I think you know,
he's obviously you know, a free agent's
responsibility to put yourself in the
best position to be successful and so
Cam gets to do that and so
that's credit to him and his journey and
the performance that he had last year. I
thought he did really good job for us
and so
you know, we'll continue to have those
conversations.
Yeah, we we know we have to build the
roster as we go and you know, again,
just so we talked about there stages to
this process in this journey and so
you know, we'll just continue to have
those conversations and I think that
that works well for everyone.
Yeah,
yeah, Luke's Luke's a really good player
and his
ability to play at center and go to
Carolina and in the division. I was a
little bummed on that part of it, but
he's going to do a really good job. He
obviously played a really valuable role
for us. We do have some guys who play
the guard position you know, that have
played the past year year and a half
probably you know, really last year that
could probably transition into this
playing some center and so we'll give
those guys opportunities through the
off-season and we'll see where it takes
us.
It's the age-old balancing act. You
know,
I think we do feel confident we have a
lot of the core pieces in place and so I
think sometimes what's important when
you have those core pieces in place is
to find the complementary pieces and so
you know, we feel like we got some
really good guys you know, ready to rock
and roll and so now it's about
complementing and tying these things
together and so
you can go out there and you have a
really balanced offense.
I think you just
part of it is evaluating the player and
then evaluating how they fit into that
puzzle piece you know, so to speak with
those with those players and so
obviously with Chris with A with all the
other guys you know,
a part of that receiver room you know,
you're kind of connecting those dots and
you know, people like to say in receiver
room you always kind of want to feel
like an NBA you know, starting five.
They all you don't want all the same
looking bodies. You know, there's a lot
of different job responsibilities that
go into it and so it's just us having
those conversations that says hey, if
this guy came into the room, this is
what it probably looks like. This is how
we structure it. If this guy again, you
got to have enough flexibility within
your scheme to be able to do that, but I
think it's important to understand what
it's going to look like with a
particular player.
>> [laughter]
>> I like watching the NBA. I'm I'm an NBA
guy.
We'll still primarily be in Metairie and
you know, once the preseason schedule
comes out, then we'll accommodate
hopefully some joint practices. That's
our goal certainly. We got to kind of
wait pending you know, hopefully the the
games that we we are hoping for.
Hopefully those come our way because we
got some plans ahead for for that just
to create some joint practice
environments. I think that's going to be
really beneficial for our team last
year. We were heavy into the scheme
installation. You know, we're kind of
putting in two new schemes
on offense and defense and so this year
I think with the continuity, I think
it's going to allow us to get some
really good work in some joint practices
and it's just a matter of us getting the
the games that hopefully will complement
that.
Yeah, I missed Clint by a year. So Clint
was there the year before I got in New
Orleans, but obviously if competing
against Clint, he's been a number spots.
I love the way he operates the systems
he brings. He's going to be really
really good head coach and obviously, I
think a great example is what they were
able to do in Seattle and the the way he
was able to create a system that worked
for those guys.
I'd say those are two independent items.
Love both of those guys at the end of
day. So love both those guys. They play
different roles.
Chris you know, special teams he's
excellent. He can play it play a role on
defense. Um
Felt felt great.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, pro days our goal ultimately Jeff
does a really good job as we just try
and get as much exposure as we can
across our entire personnel and coaching
staff.
Last week was kind of you know, you can
almost view it as our college blitz. We
kind of send everyone off
you know,
pending TSA travel and all that fun
stuff
and then get as many many guys out there
as we can and so you know, I was with
Jeff really most of the week just you
know, going to a few different spots and
so you know, it's a diverse group. It's
you know, it's not all we're not just
chasing just one particular position.
We're trying to get go to the spots and
get some exposure.
We we were a little later. We were a
little late later. So we were okay.
Well, I I think it's I think it's a
I think it's really good conversations.
I think ultimately prototypes are built
for a reason because you know, there
there's a there's a percentage chance
that you know, it's going to work and so
you know, if he is outside the
prototype, it doesn't mean we can't go
that route. We just better know like all
right, you know, if you have a team full
of exceptions, it's not going to work
very well. If you have an exception and
he is a rare special player,
you know, those can work and there's
certainly examples throughout our league
and our history of guys making that
happen. We just got to be careful when
you go down that road
>> [laughter]
>> No, I I think just obviously you got to
have production. You got to you got to
be a really productive player.
You know, if you're if you're slightly
off a prototype, you know, you got to be
a really really productive player. Have
the ability to make plays and have have
done it over a course of you know,
an extended period of time to kind of
you know, show that show showcase that
and so
you know, there's a lot of conversation
we had about that.
Yep.
Yeah.
Backup quarterbacks obviously really
really important role and Kenny did an
excellent job in Philadelphia for us.
You know, I think the first thing and
the most important thing is at the end
of day you're still the quarterback and
that you got to be prepared for your
opportunity and so Kenny's a great
example. He played
the back end of a game at Washington. He
played the next week at against Dallas
at home. Let us to a victory there and
you know, it's just a great example of
him being prepared and ready to go. And
so I think you got to start there. You
got to be prepared. You got to be ready
to go. And then there's the part of your
a part of a quarterback room and you're
part of the preparation process and it's
important that those guys can kind of
help complement the starting quarterback
and his preparation and kind of be
another set of eyes. And again, every
room's going to be structured
differently, but what he can do to help
that guy be prepared.
Yep.
Generally been happy and eating and not
Like what is it like about managing top
personalities?
Especially at that position where there
are some like egos and stuff to manage.
Like what does it take to kind of kind
of handle that type of situation?
I would say perception and reality
sometimes aren't always the same. Uh
cuz I haven't [laughter]
If what is coming out it can't be that
bad. I I really haven't come out I
haven't been around a bunch of guys that
um
we had issues with. I think you know I
think one of the traits that sometimes
makes receivers special is their
competitiveness and sometimes
competitiveness
in an emotional setting can look
different for everyone and so sometimes
people can take that as a uh a
challenging situation or a selfish
situation. Uh ultimately people just
want to be successful and help their
team win and so um you know I think it's
important to have conversations with
those guys understand their roles
understand
um
the heating moments of a game those
happen. Um you know everyone's
everyone's grown men in this
environment. We can all have those
conversations and continue to go and so
uh you know I think of uh you know a lot
of the guys that I've been fortunate to
be around uh they all want the football
but they all want the football because
they want to help us win and they think
that's one of the best ways they can do.
Do you want to be around some of those
guys in food you got to be proactive
like when you know someone's kind of
wired like that? I think I think uh
again we're all we're all men in this
process. We're all part of experience
there's a lot of different emotions and
personality types and I think it's
important to just not have an
understanding for where where everyone's
at and to have those conversations to be
had uh beforehand. Understand there's
going to be conversations in the moment
that's happened that's part of this game
and so uh
yeah I think again you know
we can have those conversations and as
long as everyone at the end of the day
understands
the focus and the goal is to ultimately
win if the focus stays there um you know
we can work with that. I'm working on a
story about what it's like when you're a
first-time head coach and you've
obviously been a high-profile college
player and worked in a market as an
assistant where everybody knows who you
are but is there a difference when
you're the head coach when you walk into
the grocery store or I mean what's it
like dealing with the celebrity of being
the boss versus other staff members?
Yeah um
You've been recognized anywhere weird?
>> Yeah no I think uh
yeah there's probably a little bit more.
You know that's just naturally comes
with the uh the territory a little bit
but uh you know I'm fortunate I'm in a
I'm in a great environment in New
Orleans it's a special place it's uh
awesome people. Uh they're all tied in
they're all in on the Saints so I think
it helps helps us with our journey. How
do you deal with that? Is it hard to be
anonymous now
in a way that maybe it wasn't 2 years
ago or 3 years ago? I think I think it's
fine. Yeah yeah I think it's fine. We're
in a good environment.
Time for one or two more here.
Hey Kelly Kelly from ESPN how are you?
Good how are you? Um I'm working on a
story about private quarterback coaches
and how players work with them and work
with them and how they work with team
coaching staffs as well.
And since you've been a quarterback
coach on you know NFL level and now head
coach and have seen that in many
different places what how do you like
what is that communication like between
the private quarterback coach and
yourself in different roles?
Yeah I think uh
you know a lot of what these
quarterbacks have done which I think is
to the benefit of our league to the
players to the organizations I think
it's a win for everyone is uh you know
during these off-season programs you
know it's really about creating
structure for the quarterbacks and
creating them an opportunity to grow and
develop as they go through the
off-season process and so I think one of
the important things is guys have found
the opportunity to say hey you know we
can work with a specific quarterback
coach maybe offsite you know that's kind
of separate from our organization which
I think is healthy for a quarterback to
kind of hear a different voice to hear a
different perspective at time and I
think the important aspect that's on the
quarterback is that you know all of this
is kind of tied together. I think the
the best situations are the ones where
you know a personal quarterback coach
really understands the system or what
the quarterback's being asked to do
within the organization and when within
the offensive scheme.
And when all three of those you know are
kind of tied together creates a really
good ecosystem and allows the
quarterback to get better during the
off-season. And I think Taysom this year
worked with
someone with QB Country in Dallas I Yes.
Um how did that how did you see that
help him as the season went on?
Yeah again I think you know during the
season sometimes it there's some benefit
just to a little bit of an extra set of
eyes but I think the off-season process
it just creates really good structure
and creates really good growth
opportunities for all of our
quarterbacks.
Thank you. Okay yep. All right guys
we're going to wrap it up here and All
right all good.
Appreciate it.